theselbycontest.com 2011-05-20

# CB2 - Privacy Policy

## getting to know you

When you make a purchase in one of our CB2 stores or answer one of our surveys, you may choose to give us basic information: name, email address, mailing address, ZIP code, phone and credit card numbers. This allows us to process your transactions more efficiently, and ultimately, to give you a higher caliber of customer service. When you visit our Web site, we may collect more information: your Internet service provider's address, the name of the Web page directing you, as well as your clicks and activity on our site. This tracking data helps us understand how to make our site more available and user friendly to our customers. 

## getting to know what you like

We also gather customer information by taking note of the purchases you make. Think of it as a concierge service where customer preferences are remembered for future consideration. By looking at your purchases in context with marketing demographics or with information from companies whose products and services you may be interested in, it helps our buyers and merchandisers continue to seek out products and designs you may find relevant and unique. Likewise, other companies may also forward to us additional names, mailing addresses, and email addresses when we have news or product offerings that may be of special interest to their customers. In order to serve you better, we may at times contract with other companies to help us process information. For instance, their assistance can help us better fulfill customer orders, manage and enhance customer data, and comply with postal regulations. For your security, these companies are bound by our non-disclosure agreements or contractual arrangements to provide privacy protection for your information. 

## information at your service

The personal information we collect is primarily intended to offer better customer service and to improve communications. The customer information from Euromarket Design's CB2 and Crate and Barrel brands is combined to provide greater security and inform customers of products and services that may interest them. When a purchased item is not immediately available, many of our customers appreciate receiving an email to update the status of their order. We also may need to contact customers by phone, postal mail, or email if questions arise regarding their orders. When you shop at a CB2 store or visit us online, it is also an opportunity for you to provide us with information and feedback that helps us continue to bring new ideas, unique products, and a creative approach to shopping for your home. 

## information secure under lock and key

We take all reasonable steps to protect our customers' personal information against loss, misuse, and alteration. We use encryption technology whenever receiving and transferring your personal information on our site. 

When you make a purchase online, either a solid key or a locked padlock icon will appear in the lower right of your browser window. This icon indicates that your transaction session is secured through Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). If one of these icons does not appear, please contact CB2 at 800.606.6252 to complete your purchase. 

## update your information

Updating your contact information is quick and easy. Just contact us, including your previous and current full name, mailing address, email address and phone number. Please understand updates may take from six to eight weeks to process from the date of request receipt. 

## information sharing

Information sharing can provide a valuable type of consumer networking. By helping to make new connections and introduce new resources to our customers, you may discover new opportunities and products compatible with your interests and needs. With that end in mind, when you purchase an item, your customer information is shared with other select companies whose products and services you may find useful.

Information sharing also helps us to guard against potential fraud and other wrongdoing. We review transactions internally on a regular basis to identify potential concerns, and we partner with select outside companies to further enhance our ability to ensure that fraudulent orders and/or potentially damaging worms, viruses and other types of malware do not interfere with our ability to provide the best possible products, value and services to you and to our other valued customers.

## information sharing is up to you

We appreciate and respect that not all customers may wish to benefit from the opportunity to share information with other select companies. If you do not want Crate and Barrel to share your customer information, please immediately contact us and we will remove your name from lists we share with other companies. After the six- to eight-week time period it takes to process your request, your information will no longer be shared. When contacting us, please clearly state your request, along with your name, mailing address, email address and phone number. Please note that this request will not prevent us from reviewing each transaction for potential wrongdoing, but it will be effective in all other instances.

It is important to understand that with some companies or online partners, for example WeddingChannel.com and our basic freight carrier AIT Worldwide Logistics, your information must be shared in order to receive their services.

For instance, when you order a large furniture item that requires Basic Freight Delivery, we send your name, address, email address and phone number to AIT, allowing you to access their online delivery scheduling system. AIT does not share your personal information with third parties; it is used strictly to coordinate and complete your shipment.

By agreeing to share information, our customers may have the opportunity to participate in a wider array of services and offerings.

## remove your name from our lists at any time

To delete your name from the CB2 email contact list, please follow these simple email opt-out instructions. To request to have your name removed from the catalog mailing list, please complete this quick catalog opt-out form. We appreciate your patience as it may take up to six to eight weeks to process your request from the date of receipt. When you make subsequent purchases at CB2, you may provide contact information for customer service only, and request that your name not be forwarded to either mailing list 

## protecting children's privacy

CB2 adheres to a strict privacy code regarding children and does not knowingly accept personal information from any child. If it is brought to our attention that a subscriber is under age, we will immediately remove all personal and identifiable information from our records in compliance with the Online Children's Privacy Protection Act of 1998. In addition, we will not disclose this information to any other companies. 

## cookies are served

"Cookies" are small amounts of data that are stored on your computer. They find their way to your browser via a Web server. They sound friendly and helpful because they are. They flag information about your activity on our Web site. This information helps us improve our site and make it friendlier and easier to use. We never use cookies to save passwords, credit card numbers or other highly confidential information. 

## partnerships

We currently contract with several online partners to help manage and optimize our Internet business and communications. We use CheetahMail to send emails that you have agreed to receive. Web cookies are used in those email messages and at our Web site to help us measure the effectiveness of those emails. You can "opt out" of this email cookie at any time by deleting your name from the CB2 email mailing list. We also contract with Omniture to help us assess visitation to our CB2 site. To do this, we place small pixel tags and cookies on our site. While these do allow Omniture to track your visits, the data retrieved cannot be used for any reason without our authorization. To review their privacy policy, please go to [www.omniture.com/en/privacy/policy](http://www.omniture.com/en/privacy/policy). Although Omniture logs the information about your visit, we control how that data may and may not be used. You can opt out of this Web site analysis tool by clicking [here](http://www.omniture.com/en/privacy/policy#optout). We contract with third-party service providers to place our advertising messages on this and other websites. These providers may collect anonymous information about your visits to our website, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other websites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry-standard technology used by most major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. They do not know the name, phone number, postal address, email address or any other personal information about the user. For more information about this practice, including privacy and confidentiality, please visit the following websites:  
<http://www.audiencescience.com/privacy>

## links to sites and services

At times, we provide links our customers may be interested in. CB2 is not responsible for these sites. If you choose to explore these sites and services, we suggest that you carefully review their individual Privacy Policies. 

## a privacy promise

We support and adhere to the guidelines and practices adopted by the Direct Marketing Association's "Privacy Promise." In so doing, we agree to comply with a customer's requests to not share their information with other companies or to contact them for marketing purposes by postal mail, telephone or email. If at any time, as a customer, you feel CB2 is not committed to its Privacy Policy, please contact us. You may also contact the DMA's Committee on Ethical Business Practices at [mgoldberger@the-dma.org](mailto:mgoldberger@the-dma.org). 

## privacy policy updates

Efforts to bring new services, ideas and partners to benefit our customers may make it necessary to amend our Privacy Policy. If this occurs, we will post the new policy on our Web site and in our stores. Once posted, the new policy will go into effect immediately, replacing any previously stated policy. 

## questions anyone?

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, we will do our best to answer them. Here's how to contact us. 

## phone

Customer Service Department  
800.606.6252  
Monday - Sunday, 7:00 a.m. - 9:00 p.m. (Central Time)

## email

## address

CB2  
Customer Service Department  
1860 W. Jefferson Avenue  
Naperville, IL 60540-3918
